HTML Sematics Questions!

1. Ask about id # tags: after following the instructions it appears as id =“about”>About

2. New tabs: after following the code instruction with target on About it only went back to Home page within the About page. Why? Should be like this?

3. Grid borders are not like in the example "square shape" on work page?

4. Button transitioning only 1 button not in example like 3 on About page?

5. The text in the body is not in the centre like in the example at About page why?